Guide to the Yale Drama Alumni Association Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Drama Alumni Association records
1956-1986
RU 80
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, reports and manuals documenting the operations and activities of the Yale Drama Alumni Association.
Yale Drama Alumni Association
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-G (YRG 22-G), Records of the Yale School of Drama student, alumni, and support organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
Arranged by type of material.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, minutes, reports and manuals documenting the operations and activities of the Yale Drama Alumni Association.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Societies, etc.
- Records concerning the Yale Drama Alumni Association, 1956-1986; Accession 1992-A-080
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
  - Manual for Alumni Associations, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yale Alumni, undated (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
  - Talent Directory, 1960-19664 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Welch Presentation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Television, undated (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Conference Book, Career Guide (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 50th Anniversary Design Exhibition, Bevau-Cole Tributes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Yale Rep Publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaire and Analysis, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter/ Memos, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Day, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Officers, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constitution-, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - McCandless-Usitt Dinner- School Honors, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 50th Anniversary Gala-Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Contacts, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes, 1956-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Envelopes, Brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Records, undated (Box 2, Folder 23 - 24)
  - Report to Yale Alumni on Alumni Activities, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 26)
  - Alumni Fund- Campaign fund-MAC Fellowship, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - YDS- Dean Search Committee '78-Newsletters- Yale Ads, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - AYA Assembly XIV- AYA Nominations-AYA Communiques, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Career Handbook - Edition #2, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes, Meetings, 1978 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Events
    - Christmas Party, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Career Cay, 1978 November
    - Wine and Cheese Party, 1979 March 29
    - Alumni Day, 1979 April 7
  - Minutes, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 33 - 35)
  - Peggy Clarke Kelley Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 36 - 39)
  - Alumni Day, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Assembly, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Yale Career Handbook, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 44 - 45)
  - Alumni II, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Cole Porter, Minutes, Officers, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Reunions, 60th Anniversary, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Questionnaires, Minutes, 60th Anniversary, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Meeting Notices, Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Career Handbook, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Envelopes, Constitution, Newsletters, Reports, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence Regarding Career Handbook, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - AYA Committees, Workshops, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Fall/ Winter, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - 40th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Fall Get-Together NYC, Yale Christmas Party, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Publications, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Report of AYA Committee on the Arts, 60th Anniversary, Cole Porter, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - 1978-82 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Executive Committee Rosters, Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Rosters Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Secretary, 1957-1965 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Minutes, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 67 - 68)
  - Minutes, Correspondence, Amended Constitution, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Addresses, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1981 November 7 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence, Minutes, 1982 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Minutes, 1982 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Addresses, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Minutes, 1982 February 2 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Yale Drama Stationary, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Guest Book, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Finished Career Handbook, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)